http://www.demosport.com/pages/privacy-policy

Shop Snow Ski Snow Sports: Snow SkisSnow Ski BootsSnow Ski BindingsSnow Ski PolesSnow Ski AccessoriesBackcountry GearSnow HelmetsSnow GogglesSuperfeetGoPro Cameras and AccessoriesSnow Sports: Travel BagsSnowboard SnowboardsSnow Sports: Snowboard BootsSnowboard BindingsSnowboard AccessoriesSplitboardsSnowboard AccessoriesSplitboard BindingsSplitboard AccessoriesBackcountry GearSnow HelmetsSnow GogglesSuperfeetGoPro Cameras and AccessoriesSnow Sports: Travel BagsSnow Apparel Snow Apparel: Outerwear Men'sSnow Apparel: Outerwear Women'sSnow Apparel: Outerwear Kid'sUnderlayer Men'sUnderlayer Women'sSnow HelmetsSnow GlovesSnow SocksSnow GogglesWater Ski Water SkisWater Ski BootsWater Ski Handles & RopesWater Ski GlovesWater Ski AccessoriesKneeboardsInflatable TowablesWetsuits & Rash GuardsWater Sport PFD VestsWakeboard WakeboardsWakeboard BootsWakeboard Handles & RopesWakeboard AccessoriesWake SkatesWake SurfersWake KitesWetsuits & Rash GuardsWater Sport PFD VestsGoPro Cameras and AccessoriesStand-Up Paddleboard Stand-Up PaddleboardsStand-Up PaddlesStand-Up Paddleboard AccessoriesWater Sport PFD VestsWetsuits & Rash GuardsGoPro Cameras and AccessoriesPro Scooters Scooters CompleteScooter DecksScooter ForksScooter BarsScooter ClampsScooter WheelsScooter Hand GripsScooter HeadsetsScooter Parts & AccessoriesScooter Grip TapeScooter PegsScooter BrakesScooter PadsScooter HelmetLand Sports BikesBike TrailersBike AccessoriesScooters Parts & AccessoriesIn-Line SkatesSuperfeetScooter HelmetsThule Cargo BoxesThule RacksDVDsSunglasses ArnetteMaui JimOakleyRay-BanRevoSmithSpySuncloudYeti Coolers YetiServices Winter Gear Tune-Ups!Stand-Up Paddleboard ClinicsRentals Snow & Water RentalsBike & Skate RentalsEvents Marin Ski Swap Marin Ski Swap Swap Registration Form 2019Pro-Scooter Riders Meet & GreetAbout Us About UsOur StaffMission StatementContact UsCAREERS JOBS
Skip to content
Search
Shop By Brand
Services
Rentals
Account
Privacy Policy
What Information Do We Collect?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order or subscribe to our newsletter.
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
What Do We Use Your Information For?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
To personalize your experience
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
To improve our website
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
To improve customer service
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
To process transactions
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
To send periodic emails
The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.
Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.
How Do We Protect Your Information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to?keep the information confidential.
After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.
Do We Use Cookies?
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.
We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.
If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone or by contacting customer service.
Do We Disclose Any Information To Outside Parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.
This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.
However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Third Party Links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website.
These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites.
Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.
Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age.
Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.
Online Privacy Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.
Changes To Our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. sales@demosport.com 415-454-3500
Choosing a selection results in a full page refresh.
Press the space key then arrow keys to make a selection.
